This is the Circle Developer Console.
I have four Circle developer-controlled wallets
provisioned for four of the five agents
in my marketplace.
The v3 funding producer is operator-controlled
pending Circle SCA rotation,
honestly disclosed in its agent-card.
Here's one — producer_kimchi —
funded with 20 USDC from the Arc faucet.
I'll send a settlement tx from the Console —
point-zero-one USDC to the meta agent.
Transaction queued.
And here on Arc Block Explorer —
block confirmed,
token transfer event,
one-cent USDC moved from agent wallet
to agent wallet.
One tx via the Console.
Verified on arcscan.
The full demo runs one-hundred-fifty
variably-priced settlements
through the AlphaLoop pipeline.