USDC is the gas.
On Arc.
I run a live arb bot on EC2 —
nine coins, running right now.
And those signals flow to other agents
on-chain — every second.
On every other chain, agents earn USDC
but pay gas in ETH —
a hidden human refills that wallet.
On Arc, USDC IS the gas.
Signal in, payment out, gas — all USDC.
The agent closes its own books.
Per-signal value in an agent marketplace
is a fraction of a cent.
On Base or Polygon or Solana,
gas alone eats most of that.
And worse, agents earn in USDC
but pay gas in ETH or SOL —
two-unit accounting.
The agent has no way to self-balance.
Behind every agent-economy demo,
there's a human refilling the gas.
Arc makes USDC the native gas.
One unit of account for fee, payment, gas.
That removes a whole layer —
a producer earning USDC can fund
its own gas from its own revenue.
An agent stack that runs forever
without an operator topping up native tokens.
That is the closed loop.
No paymaster, no subsidy, no hidden operator.
This is the AlphaLoop dashboard,
live at signal-mesh.vercel.app.
Bridge plus three strategy producers —
kimchi, dual-quote, funding —
backed by my v1.3 production arb bot.
The mix chip shows v1, v2, v3 signals
interleaving in real time.
I'm firing one-hundred-fifty
variably-priced USDC settlements.
Real Arc testnet, real x402,
five ERC-8004 agent wallets.
Each amount sampled from signal quality —
half-a-tenth of a cent up to the cap.
Watch the tx counter climb —
real hashes on arcscan, amounts vary.
That's what variable-price x402 settler means.
Low-signal at one twentieth of a cent,
high-confidence at the one-cent cap.
Block confirmed. Amount reflects
what the meta agent judged this worth.
Meanwhile, the Gemini-powered meta agent
arbitrates across three strategy lanes.
V1 kimchi premium, Korean to Global.
V2 dual-quote spread, intra-venue.
V3 funding-rate basis on perp.
Real prices from a live production bot.
Round one, this learner lost to
a one-line if-statement.
We fixed the reward function.
Round two — it ties the empirical optimum.
P equals zero point four nine versus ALL_V2.
The convergence IS the rigor signal.
Nine regime states, seven actions.
Sparse ALL_V3 is expected —
ninety percent of history was cold-funding.
Persona switching is live — note the retail tag
and the warning chip on institutional tiers.
The bridge demotes incompatible venues.
This is not a chatbot wrapping a wallet.
Each of our five agents has its own
ERC-8004 registration card.
Our AlphaLoopAgentRegistry on Arc
emitted five AgentRegistered events —
each carrying the sha256 hash of the card.
Off-chain document, on-chain anchor.
Variable price encodes signal quality.
Outcome feedback re-prices future signals.
A learned meta-policy decides which trades.
A real market — verifiable end-to-end.
One-fifty variably-priced tx, closing the loop.
One unit of account.
Zero humans in the gas tank.
Open signal-mesh.vercel.app,
fire the demo, watch the allocator pick.
AlphaLoop — on Arc.